Amanda Sealshaw. Things I learned this week. Yeah. So did you know that lobster was once
considered like garbage food? It was even like the Native American tribes who use lobster shells
as fertilizer. Like they really didn't even like eat the animal. They was like, yeah, we just need
the shells or whatever. What ended up turning into this being like a high dollar situation was that
the railroad companies started to develop lobster on their dining carts because it was cheap to get.
They started saying to the people inland, like, yeah, lobster is popping. And so that's how that
shift happened. I didn't know this, but online users have apparently uncovered a trend where many U.S.
State Departments of Corrections, most notably Texas and New Jersey, are misclassifying Black people as
white in police records in a ploy to seem less racist. That's crazy. Like literally to try and
look like they're not over arresting Black people. They're just logging very obviously Black people
as white. And it distorts the statistics and obscures the realities of racial profiling
faced by Black communities in the U.S. Those are my things I learned this week. Remember to hit me up
with yours, 1-855-AMAND-8. That's 1-855-262-6328. I'd love to hear what you learned.
We are, we are, we are.